Myles Rangel

Vacaville, Ca

Phone: (559)356-7299 | Email: myles.rangel@gmail.com

Currently a Freelance Web Developer, working various projects. I am currently enjoying the MERN stack. However, I am profecient in many more technologies and always looking to improve. I am a college graduate with a Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and a Military Veteran with 5+ years experience as a dedicated leader.

Skills

Front-End	Back End	Source Control	FrameWorks	UI/UX
Javascript ES6 / jQuery	REST / MySQL	Git(Git Flow)	React / Redux	Wireframing / UML
CSS / SASS / LESS	PHP / AWS	SCRUM / Agile	Bootstrap	Prototyping
HTML / XHTML / Jade	Apache / Node	Github	AngularJS	Adobe Suite
Webpack / 508 Accessibility		Trello / Bitbucket		User Stories

Professional Experience

Freelance Full Stack Web Developer

June 2018 - Present | Remote

- → Maintains existing websites and provides updates to help with system flexibility.
- →Executed prototypes in React in ES6 with Node and MySQL.
- →Coordinated closely with clients on software needs and updates to current software.
- →Meet with potential clients to discuss software needs. Create various wireframes and mock-ups for visual aids.

Clock Specialty / Web Developer

June 2017 – June 2018 | Remote

- →Implemented new check-in/check-out system with HTML, CSS, PHP and MySQL.
- →Created Website using HTML, CSS, PHP, Javascript and Bootstrap.
- →Coordinated closely with various mockup and design palletes.

Personal Projects

Personal Website

- →Written with Reactis, Javascript, HTML, CSS, Node
- →Dependencies include: body-parser, cors, express and nodemailer

Clock Specialty

- →90's themed clock shop, using HTML, CSS, Node and Javascript
- →Dependencies include: express, now and cors
- →Web Scraper to display 'find your perfect clock today!' results. Results are cached in an Object

Education

California State University East Bay / Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

2012 - 2017 : Hayward, CA